<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonas Schropp</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jonas Schropp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>admintools</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-06-13-admintools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-06-13-admintools/</guid>
      <description>When I started freelancing, I quickly realized that administration and project management eat into your time like nothing else. Many days I would spend more than half my working time on tasks that did not generate any income &amp;ndash; answering emails, managing appointments, recording when I worked for how long on what and writing invoices.
Over time I went from filling every invoice and time sheet by hand in word, via paying for an overpriced online time tracking and invoicing tool to using a custom R package for administration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Of Scurvy in the Army</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-04-01-of-scurvy-in-the-army/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-04-01-of-scurvy-in-the-army/index/</guid>
      <description>Introduction or The War in Crimea It feels quite weird to start blogging. I don&amp;rsquo;t use Instagram, Twitter, Facebook or Tiktok. I like to turn my phone silent during the day. I don&amp;rsquo;t particularly enjoy advertising myself online, but I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot by reading hundreds (if not thousands) of blog posts over the years and this seems like the best way to share my own thoughts and ideas. In long form rather than 140 characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hillary vs. the Donald</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-08-09-hillary-vs-td/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-08-09-hillary-vs-td/</guid>
      <description>Intro In 2016 I was studying Psychology at the University of Innsbruck, and I had no idea where to go afterwards. I had just finished my Bachelor’s thesis knew one thing: I wasn’t made for clinical psychology. I didn’t really want to work with patients. But I also had discovered the research process, and I felt there might be a path forwards for me within science.
What interested me most was how modern big data technologies could be applied to questions in Psychology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
